let questionArray = [
    {
       "question": "What colours are represented on the Norwegian flag?",
       "answers": {
          "correctAnswer": "Red, blue and white",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Yellow, blue and white",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Red and white",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Blue and white"
       }
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the national day of Norway?",
       "answers": {
          "correctAnswer": "17th of May",
          "wrongAnswer1": "20th of May",
          "wrongAnswer2": "17th of April",
          "wrongAnswer3": "20th of April"
       }
    },
    {
       "question": "What is the population of Norway?",
       "answers": {
          "correctAnswer": "5,3 million",
          "wrongAnswer1": "4,3 million",
          "wrongAnswer2": "4,8 million",
          "wrongAnswer3": "5,8 million"
       }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the capital of Norway?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "Oslo",
         "wrongAnswer1": "Helsinki",
         "wrongAnswer2": "Stockholm",
         "wrongAnswer3": "København"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "What is the currency of Norway?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "Krone",
         "wrongAnswer1": "Euro",
         "wrongAnswer2": "Nordikyn",
         "wrongAnswer3": "Shilling"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "Which of these organizations are Norway not a part of?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "The European Union (EU)",
         "wrongAnswer1": "World Trade Organization (WTO)",
         "wrongAnswer2": "United Nations (UN)",
         "wrongAnswer3": "North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO)"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "What is the name of the current King of Norway?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "King Harald V",
         "wrongAnswer1": "King Olav III",
         "wrongAnswer2": "King Ludwig II",
         "wrongAnswer3": "King Edvard X"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "On June 7, 1905, Norway became officially independent from which country?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "Sweden",
         "wrongAnswer1": "Great Britain",
         "wrongAnswer2": "Denmark",
         "wrongAnswer3": "Germany"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "Which side did Norway officially support during World War II?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "Neutral",
         "wrongAnswer1": "Allied powers",
         "wrongAnswer2": "Axis powers",
         "wrongAnswer3": "United States of America"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "The indigenous people of Norway are known as…",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "Sami",
         "wrongAnswer1": "Maya",
         "wrongAnswer2": "Tuareg",
         "wrongAnswer3": "Tatars"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "Which Nobel Prize is awareded in Norway each year?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "Peace",
         "wrongAnswer1": "Literature",
         "wrongAnswer2": "Chemistry",
         "wrongAnswer3": "Medicine"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "What is the unofficial national dish of Norway?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "Grandiosa frozen pizza",
         "wrongAnswer1": "Taco",
         "wrongAnswer2": "Meatballs",
         "wrongAnswer3": "Jose Ole burritos"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "Every year since 1947, Norway has presented England with…",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "A Christmas tree for Trafalgar Square",
         "wrongAnswer1": "A pair of wooden shoes for the British Museum",
         "wrongAnswer2": "An olive branch for the Prime Minister’s office",
         "wrongAnswer3": "An honorary Norwegian passport for a British citizen"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "Which countries does Norway border?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "With Sweden, Finland and Russia",
         "wrongAnswer1": "With Sweden and Finland",
         "wrongAnswer2": "Only Sweden",
         "wrongAnswer3": "With Sweden, Denmark and Finland"
      }
   },
   {
      "question": "Which famous painting was drawn by norwegian artist Edward Munch?",
      "answers": {
         "correctAnswer": "The Scream",
         "wrongAnswer1": "The Last Supper",
         "wrongAnswer2": "Girl With a Pearl Earring",
         "wrongAnswer3": "The Night Watch"
      }
   },
 ]